{
    "id": "1772533005a94a7f97082d979993e113",
    "title": "Articles Or No Articles",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He died …………………….",
            "description": "No article is used in this expression.",
            "answers": [
                "at sea",
                "at the sea",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d9cf1e86d11f431fb2720e66ef7ea001"
        },
        {
            "question": "I met some interesting people at ……………………….",
            "description": "In American English, university is usually used with the article 'the'. In British English, 'the' can be omitted before university. ",
            "answers": [
                "university",
                "the university",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "51465b72a2db41da856afae181912ea6"
        },
        {
            "question": "He left …………………………….. in the morning and never came back.",
            "description": "No article is used before home. ",
            "answers": [
                "home",
                "the home",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2186ab60c0a44e20afd183be8e61941a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I regret leaving ………………………….. at fourteen.",
            "description": "No article is used in the expression leave school. ",
            "answers": [
                "school",
                "the school",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "e61c50d5a57c4479938f0c6e4d31e01b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I will meet you at ……………………………",
            "description": "We use the article here because the college is just a meeting place.",
            "answers": [
                "college",
                "the college",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9226ea9365924a67ba2381d5378eb894"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was surprised at the amount of ……………………………. collected.",
            "description": "'The' is dropped after ‘the amount of’.",
            "answers": [
                "money",
                "the money",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3e2f47280f5541e9b8b8f895eef9e7af"
        },
        {
            "question": "He went to ……………………………… in Cambridge.",
            "description": "No article is normally used in this expression.",
            "answers": [
                "college",
                "the college",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dd5521475bee431a982d275d5aa253a9"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is time the children went to …………………………..",
            "description": "No article is used in the expression 'go to bed'.",
            "answers": [
                "bed",
                "the bed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "028de1a94d46472a926fbdd5881add28"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t feel like getting out of …………………………",
            "description": "No article is used in this expression.",
            "answers": [
                "bed",
                "the bed",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ef1523b0ef3545ddb5ef0d840a4ccf92"
        },
        {
            "question": "He is collecting money for …………………………….",
            "description": "The blind means all blind people. The article ‘the’ is required in this expression.",
            "answers": [
                "blind",
                "the blind",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cdcd2c90aea244639f7782157dc64a3b"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………… criminals are non-violent.",
            "description": "When most means the majority of, it is used without the.",
            "answers": [
                "Most",
                "The most",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3340ab601d6943669450f0eb9bbafc8f"
        },
        {
            "question": "He could play …………………………. when he was just five.",
            "description": "Articles are always used with the names of musical instruments.",
            "answers": [
                "piano",
                "the piano",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9db0ed8df08f480ca2b78c09a3822235"
        }
    ]
}